# Natasha Whitehead

(905) 758-1972

738 Firth Court, Newmarket, Ontario, L3Y 8H8 natasha.whitehead4@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY:**

Motivated and eager IT Professional with programing and design experience. Dedication and determination to make sure the job is done with integrity and quality. Effective use of time management and organization skills are utilized to identify and problem solve efficiently. Reliable, always early, and will put in the extra time to get the job done.

# **OBJECTIVE:**

To pursue co-op work employment as an Information Technology Professional

#### **QUALIFICATIONS:**

Programming Languages:
 Java, SQL, HTML, CSS, PHP

• Design Software Applications: Flash, Photoshop, Premiere, and After Effects

Office Applications:
 Hardware Applications:
 Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access
 Scanners, Printers, Hard Drives

• Certifications: WorkSmart Certificate, Smart Serve Certificate

#### **STRENGTHS:**

Dependable ~ Responsible ~ Attention to Detail

#### **EDUCATION:**

Currently enrolled at Georgian college for Computer Programmer Analyst

Fanshawe College for Multimedia Design (1 year)

Ontario Secondary School Diploma (Honours)

Sir William Mulock Secondary School Newmarket, Ontario

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE:**

ROGERS TV, Newmarket ON,

Winter 2010

Developed communication, stress management, organization skills:

- Operating the VTR, camera's audio table, and colour adjuster
- Setting up and taking down equipment
- Keeping equipment organized
- Keeping contact with others to make sure the right shot is taken

# NEWMARKET SOCCER CLUB, Newmarket ON,

2008

Developed organization, teamwork, interpersonal, stress management, and problem solving skills:

- Assisted with registration, administration, and officiating
- Monitored and checked that the schedules were correct and on time
- Assisted the coach in preparing, organizing, and demonstrating drills
- Maintained an orderly training environment
- Explained practice routines to parents

#### OUT OF THE COLD, Toronto ON,

Winter of 2006-2007

Developed empathy and understanding of personal circumstances:

- Assisted the foot doctor to treat the homeless people's feet
  - Organized the medications and supplies
  - · Sanitized used instruments

# Natasha Whitehead

(905) 758-1972

738 Firth Court, Newmarket, Ontario, L3Y 8H8 natasha.whitehead3@gmail.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

WILD WING, Aurora ON,

2013-Present

Developed interpersonal, responsibility, working independently and efficiency skills:

- Ensured float was accurate and correct amount was made
- Responsible for ensuring people's safety
- Managed 15 tables at once
- Creating a great and memorable environment

#### TEAM FSU, Newmarket ON,

2006-Present

Developed office administration and management skills,

- Operator of sorting and distributing greeting cards
- Filed and performed other office duties as assigned

# OLIVER'S COFFEE, Bracebridge ON,

2012

Developed initiative, memorization, and adaptability skills:

- Created a friendly and inviting environment for customers
- Ensured orders were made to customers satisfaction
- Ensured work was always being done
- Knowledgeable about the products
- Assisted customers to their tables

# MCDONALDS, Newmarket ON,

2009-2012

Developed teamwork, problem solving, safety, and communication:

- Establishing a productive and efficient environment
- · Ensure everything is stocked and organized
- Ensure that all of the equipment is clean and working properly
- Created a clean and safe environment for both workers and customers
- Solving problems and clarifying issues with equipment and/or people

#### **AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS:**

•	Dean's list first semester at Georgian College	2013
•	Dean's list first semester at Fanshawe College	2011
•	Most Valuable Media Arts Artist award in Highschool	2010
•	Photography Award in Highschool	2010
•	Played on one of the top ten women's soccer teams in Ontario	2007-2010
•	Scholarship offers for soccer	2010

~ REFERENCES AVALIABLE UPON REQUEST ~